rewardtv.com 2013-08-23

# Privacy Policy - Terms & Conditions - RewardTV

|  | 

Privacy Policy Last Updated 06/27/13

| 

  * Introduction

  * Types of Information Collected

  * How Information is Collected

  * How Information is Used

  * With Whom Information is Shared

| 

  * A Note to Parents

  * Notification of Changes and Your Acceptance

  * Correcting/Updating Personal Information

  * Contact Member Services

  * Show all

---|---  
  
Introduction - Our Commitment to Privacy

We do not send unsolicited emails. We also do not sell email addresses to third party marketers.

Your name, address, email address, phone number, and other personally identifiable information are not sold to third party marketers.

Types of Information Collected

The following are the types of information we collect:

Whenever you register to become a Member, RewardTV collects from you some personal information, including your name, email address, physical address, birth date, gender, zip code or other similar information. When you play a RewardTV Game anywhere on the Internet, you may be asked questions regarding your television and advertising viewing preferences, and your responses are collected by us. You must be at least 13 years of age to become a Member (see "A Special Note to Parents Concerning Privacy" below).

Depending upon how you visit RewardTV, we may automatically collect a log file which contains your IP address, browser type, domain name, click-stream data and the time of your visit. This information is used to measure and analyze RewardTV usage and performance. In addition, when you visit a third-party site with which RewardTV has a marketing relationship, we may assign a randomly generated number and store that information as a browser cookie. The random number stored contains no non-public personal information about you or your machine. We may cause our servers to query that cookie and to log the random number along with the time and along with other data supplied to us. This information is used to better understand and serve RewardTV members. Data from unregistered users is not tracked, used or published by us in any context for any purpose. Unregistered users cannot play RewardTV games. If you are a RewardTV member, data collected from your use of RewardTV and third party sites with which we have a marketing relationship may be aggregated with data from other RewardTV members and such aggregate data about our members may be published, but no such published information will contain any personally-identifiable information about you.

How Information Is Collected

We collect information from you in several different areas or ways on RewardTV, including those described below:

You can currently register at our Website, Mobile Site, and through our Facebook game application. Before using RewardTV, you will be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information. You may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features RewardTV may offer, including, but not limited to, games, contests, sweepstakes, auctions and surveys.

When you play a RewardTV Game, you may be asked questions regarding your television and advertising viewing preferences.

We may operate sweepstakes, contests, instant win games, and auctions through RewardTV which may require separate registration, additional information or answers to certain questions.

We will request personally identifiable information from you via Surveys or Voting polls. Participation is always voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information. At times, you may have to register to vote or to take part in a survey.

We may offer free newsletters to share information with you about RewardTV. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered at RewardTV. We keep a record of what emails you opt to, and opt not to, receive from RewardTV. You may opt in or out of receiving email from RewardTV at any time by signing into the Website, clicking on "My Account," clicking on "View or Edit Your Member Profile," logging into your account, and checking or unchecking the boxes listed under "Email Notification" and "Auction Notification." In some instances, you may also opt in or out of receiving email from RewardTV in the designated area of certain newsletters or emails. When you open an HTML-formatted email (a message that includes graphics) from RewardTV, we include a Web Beacon (an electronic image known as a "single-pixel GIF") that will send us a confirmation that you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities.

The "Sign Up a Friend" program allows you the opportunity to earn additional Points by inviting your friends to join RewardTV. The email addresses you submit to the program are sent a one-time email invitation to register at RewardTV. The email addresses are stored solely for the purpose of sending the email invitations and tracking any subsequent registrations at RewardTV so we may award you additional Points you earn as a result of these referrals. The email addresses are not disclosed to any third parties and will not be sent any other emails from RewardTV unless the email address owners opt in to receive such mailings at the time of registration. Your friends may contact us at <http://www.rewardtv.com/help/services.sdo> to request that we remove their information from our database.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of Internet or mobile transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

In order to manage our panel and to enhance your experience as a Nielsen panelist, we place cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. The cookie that we use to recognize you as a Nielsen Panel Member when you return to this Website or visit other Nielsen panel websites employs a technology called "Flash." The information gathered via this cookie may be associated with other Nielsen cookies that you have on your computer and used to supplement the information that we have about you. This cookie does not contain any personally-identifiable information. We may also use "non-Flash" cookies or a small piece of code (sometimes referred to as "1x1 clear pixel," "Web beacon" or "clear GIF") to help us gather additional information about your Internet usage, including other websites that you visit. On occasion, we may also use non-Flash cookies to understand your exposure to certain Internet advertisements as you surf the Web. To opt out of this explicitly, please [click here](http://pt.rewardtv.com/optinout.do?oo=cancel&tu=http://www.rewardtv.com/help/privacy.sdo?optout=false).

Additionally, we may allow our panel recruitment partners to use Web beacons and cookies on our Website's registration pages solely for payment verification purposes. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by RewardTV and members of the Nielsen family of companies only and does not cover the use of cookies by any of our partners.

You can set your browser to reject non-Flash cookies, or delete individual or all non-Flash cookies on your computer by following the browser help file directions. For information about how to delete the Flash cookie, please [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). Setting your browser to reject cookies or deleting cookies, however, may interfere with your using some features of other websites and may impair your ability to participate in activities at our Website.

Certain pages on the Website and Mobile Site reside on third-party websites but are displayed within the frame of our Sites ("Co-branded Pages"). The pages within the TV Listings section of our Sites are Co-branded Pages that reside on Zap2It.com (Tribune Media Services). The information collected in the TV Listings section is shared with Zap2It.com (Tribune Media Services) solely for the purpose of providing you with customized daily television listings.

When you visit a third-party website with which we have a marketing relationship or when you visit a website displaying content (including advertisements) of a third party with which we have a marketing relationship, we may assign a randomly generated number and store that information as a browser cookie. The random number stored contains no personal information about you or your computer. We may cause our software to query that cookie and to log the random number along with the time and along with other data supplied to us. The ways in which we use these data are described above in the section entitled "Site Usage Information."

You should be aware that when you are on our Website or Mobile Site you could be directed to other websites beyond our control. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement, the click may take you off RewardTV onto a different website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use RewardTV's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to RewardTV, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

How Information is Used

RewardTV may use personal information in a number of ways, including:

  * To verify your identity at the time you register to become a RewardTV member.
  * To personalize your experience on the Sites.
  * To provide you with customer service.
  * To notify you if you are a potential winner of a prize.
  * To fulfill a prize you have won or a reward you have redeemed.
  * To announce the winner of a sweepstakes, contest, instant win game or other promotion.
  * To send your friends a one-time email invitation from the "Sign Up a Friend" Program with your permission.
  * To prepopulate sections of online forms which you may be asked to complete.
  * To determine which advertisements will appear on your screen when you access the Sites.
  * To send you newsletters, promotional messages, product announcements, and other communications from RewardTV that may be of interest to you. You may opt in or out of receiving email from RewardTV at any time by signing into the Website, clicking on "My Account," clicking on "View or Edit Your Member Profile," logging into your account, and checking or unchecking the boxes listed under "Email Notification" and "Auction Notification."
  * To improve the performance and promotions at RewardTV by measuring and analyzing aggregate demographics, interests, and usage of specific areas of the Sites and any other platforms on which RewardTV may appear.
  * To support the operation of the Sites (such as billing, account maintenance, and record-keeping), troubleshoot problems, and resolve disputes.
  * To monitor compliance with our Membership Agreement and RewardTV Program Rules.

We do not share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties for their promotional use.

A Special Note to Parents Concerning Privacy

The Website is a general audience site. We do not currently collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 at either the Website or the Mobile Site. If in the future, Nielsen decides to collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.).

Notification of Changes and Your Acceptance of the Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the home page of the Website, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our Website's home page.

Correcting/Updating Personal Information

If your registration information changes (such as your zip code), or if you no longer desire to access RewardTV, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us. This can be done by making changes to your profile. You can edit your profile by signing into your RewardTV account and visiting the "My Account" section. Click on "View or Edit Your Member Profile," make any necessary changes to your account, and then click "Update My Profile." If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of RewardTV, you can contact us by email at privacy@rewardtv.com or by postal mail at Nielsen Call Center, 501 Brooker Creek Blvd, Oldsmar, FL 34677.

You have successfully changed your status to "Total Opt-Out User." RewardTV will not collect any data at all regarding your exposure to online advertising. Please note that you will need to change your status to "Total Opt-Out User" each time you delete your cookies.

Your Opt-Out status has now been cancelled. Please refer to the Privacy and Cookie Policy for further information on the data we collect.
